{
    "id": "73aab53e94344f1c980dfd005057be3c",
    "title": "If Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It would be nice if you ............................... me a bit with the housework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "help",
                "helped",
                "had helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7705695e37a74a258f300a6be0cf74b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would get up earlier if there .................................... a good reason to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91cf20f998e5424198934fa4e2136a93"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I have enough time tomorrow, I .................................... and see you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will come",
                "would come",
                "would have come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "234e544295a24bf8bfb7e3550583c36e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ...................................... to learn a musical instrument, you have to practice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wanted",
                "had wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f64f6c16701484c8d7fd84bb129fad6"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you eat too much, you ...................................... fat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "would get",
                "will be getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f37e7ad049f34b13a36a73cd424a8975"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ........................................ here before eight, we can catch the early train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "got",
                "had gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb27ad0c31624ec2a38582ac19341257"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I .................................. you, we would both be happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "marry",
                "marrried",
                "had married"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a5894552909473f9ffa593e6ca05c15"
        },
        {
            "question": "If my nose were a little longer, I ................................. quite beautiful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2eb589022fab4ec5ad1d8e6b2ca37e03"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you .................................... me, I would have told you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have asked",
                "asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af5cca2ad9e340c09c5b0287d5d9b938"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would have been in bad trouble if he .................................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "haven't helped",
                "hadn't helped",
                "wouldn't help"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95d6bc92f0d54298a9921168a54d83aa"
        }
    ]
}